{
    "subject": "resource/T._S._Eliot",
    "predicate": "ontology/notableWork",
    "object": "resource/The_Love_Song_of_J._Alfred_Prufrock",
    "human_readable": "T.S. Eliot's notable work is 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.945899248123169,
            "question": "What type of work is 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8659292459487915,
            "question": "What is the significance of the title 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8649097084999084,
            "question": "Who is the author of 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8428144454956055,
            "question": "What is the title of T.S. Eliot's most notable work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7895567417144775,
            "question": "Who is J. Alfred Prufrock?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7615618109703064,
            "question": "What are some common themes explored in 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7583093643188477,
            "question": "Can you describe the style and tone of 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6608741879463196,
            "question": "Which literary work is associated with T.S. Eliot?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.652298092842102,
            "question": "How has 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock' influenced modern literature?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48487207293510437,
            "question": "What historical period influenced T.S. Eliot and his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=T.S. Eliot's notable work is 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8140_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock' influenced modern literature?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8140_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which literary work is associated with T.S. Eliot?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8140_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the style and tone of 'The Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8140_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8140_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide sufficient information to support that T.S. Eliot\u2019s notable work is indeed \u201cThe Love Song of J. Alfred Prufrock.\u201d Multiple documents mention this poem, describing its themes and setting it as a significant piece in Eliot's body of work."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}